https://www.abs.gov.au/website-privacy-copyright-and-disclaimer#copyright-and-creative-commons

Skip to main content
Breadcrumb Home Website privacy, copyright and disclaimer
Search ABS
Website privacy, copyright and disclaimerThis page contains information about website privacy. For information about the ABS and privacy see ABS privacy policy summary Website privacyInformation we collectWhen visiting this site, a record of your visit is logged. The following information is supplied by your browser (for example Internet Explorer) and collected by us:type of browser usedserver address (i.e. IP address which is stored anonymously)operating system (for example Windows, MAC)the date and time you accessed the sitetime spent on pagespages and links visited, and documents downloadedthe path you took to get to the sitedevice screen size and typeregion, country and preferred language settings. Why we collect it and how we use itWe use the above information to understand how our website is being used. This helps us improve our website and provide you with a better experience.EmailsWhen you email us personal information or provide it to us through 'contact us' options on this site:we will record your email address and any other information submittedwe will use this information for the purpose for which you provide ityour email address will not be added to a mailing list unless provided by you specifically for that purpose.If you fail to provide us with a minimum level of information (usually marked with an asterisk and generally, an email address), we may not be able to respond to you.We will not share your personal informationThe law, including the Privacy Act 1988, protects your personal information.Your personal information will not be disclosed to any other person, body or agency unless:you give us permissionit is authorised or required by lawit meets one of the other exceptions in the Australian Privacy Principles.For information about the ABS and privacy see ABS privacy policy summary.The ABS uses secure HTTPS connections for all of its websites. HTTPS is used to secure and protect personal or identifiable information which may be entered by customers on our contact forms and survey account forms. Customers can enjoy the wealth of data and information provided by the ABS, secure in the knowledge that any personal information is protected.The ABS does not disclose personal information overseas.How we store informationWe store information in different ways, including:our document and records management systemscloud storagebrowser storagecookies.We use cookies (small files stored on your device) created both by us and third parties. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your browser settings. However, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the website.
DisclaimerThis website is presented by the Australian Government for the purpose of disseminating information for the benefit of the public.The Australian Government has taken great care to ensure the information on this website is as correct and accurate as possible. The information on this website is also updated regularly.However, the Australian Government does not guarantee, and accepts no legal liability whatsoever arising from, or connected to, the use of any material contained on this website or on any linked site.The Australian Government recommends that users exercise their own skill and care with respect to their use of this website and that users carefully evaluate the accuracy, currency, completeness and relevance of the material on this website for their purposes.This website is not a substitute for independent professional advice and users should obtain any appropriate professional advice relevant to their particular circumstances.Cultural sensitivitiesUsers are warned that historic content on this site may contain language or views which, reflecting the authors' attitudes or that of the period in which the item was written, may be considered to be inappropriate or offensive today.Non-ABS dataThis website may include data sourced from organisations other than the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS). The inclusion of non-ABS data does not constitute either an endorsement or a recommendation by the ABS of this material. Where appropriate, the ABS will indicate non-ABS sourced data.The material on this website may include the views or recommendations of third parties, which do not necessarily reflect the views of the Australian Government, or indicate its commitment to a particular course of action.Links to external websitesThis website contains links to other websites that are external to the ABS. The ABS takes reasonable care in linking websites but has no direct control over the content of the linked sites, nor the changes that may occur to the content on those sites. It is the responsibility of the user to make their own decisions about the accuracy, currency, reliability and correctness of information contained in linked external websites.Links to external websites do not constitute an endorsement or a recommendation of any material on those sites or of any third party products or services offered by, from or through those sites. Users of links provided by this website are responsible for being aware of which organisation is hosting the website they visit.Security of the ABS websiteThe ABS applies a range of security controls to protect its website from unauthorised access. However, users should be aware that the World Wide Web is an unsecure public network that gives rise to a potential risk that a user's transactions are being viewed, intercepted or modified by third parties or that files which the user downloads may contain computer viruses, disabling codes, worms or other devices or defects.The Australian Government accepts no liability for any interference with or damage to a user's computer system, software or data occurring in connection with or relating to this website or its use. Users are encouraged to take appropriate and adequate precautions to ensure that whatever is selected from this site is free of viruses or other contamination that may interfere with or damage the user's computer system, software or data.Email addresses on the ABS websiteThe presence of email addresses on the ABS website does not infer consent to send unsolicited commercial electronic messages (email) to those addresses. Copyright and creative commonsABS Copyright© Commonwealth of AustraliaThe Commonwealth owns the copyright in all material produced by the Australian Bureau of Statistics (ABS).Apart from any use as permitted under the Copyright Act 1968, and those explicitly granted below, all other rights are reserved.All material presented on this website is provided under a Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International licence, with the exception of:the Commonwealth Coat of Armsthe ABS logomaterial protected by a trade markunit record data (microdata)content supplied by third parties.ABS also prepares customised data reports provided to individual clients. Most of these reports also carry a Creative Commons Attribution licence. Licensing details will be clearly displayed within each product. Where no indication of licensing is provided within the product, full copyright terms will apply.The details of the relevant licence conditions are available on the Creative Commons website, as is the full legal code for the CC BY 4.0 licence.Third party copyrightWherever a third party holds copyright in material presented on this website, the copyright remains with that party. Their permission may be required to use the material.This department has made all reasonable efforts to:clearly label material where the copyright is owned by a third partyensure that the copyright owner has consented to this material being presented on this website.Using the Commonwealth Coat of Arms Terms of use for the Coat of Arms are available on this website.For advice regarding reproduction and rights in ABS products and services please contact us. AttributionMaterial obtained from this website is to be attributed to this department. If you use ABS material, there are certain obligations you must fulfil. Details on how to do this can be found in Attributing ABS material.Where your use of ABS material requires citation, see How to cite ABS sources for advice. AccessibilityWe are committed to providing information and services to the widest possible audience.We are working to comply with the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG) 2.1 to Level AA, which describe how to make web content more usable and accessible for everyone. We want to provide our information for everyone, including people with a disability.We’re always improving our website and will continue to explore different ways to make it easy for you to get information. If there's information you need that you can’t get, please contact us.Known issuesProblems that we are aware of and are working to fix:some tables on this site do not currently conform to WCAG 2.1 level AA  some pages on this site are not responsive to different mobile devices.   Contact usEmail: client.services@abs.gov.auPost: Client servicesAustralian Bureau of StatisticsLocked Bag 10BELCONNEN ACT 2616
Back to top of the page
arrow-downarrow-leftarrow-rightarrow-upcav-downcav-rightclosedownloadexternal-linkfeedbackfilemenusearchsign-checksign-infosign-warningsocial-facebooksocial-instagramsocial-twittertriangle-down
